The Day When I was Born
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
I will lose my motivation if you are like that!
You always tell me to work hard...
I was so motivated...
But you repeat it, I have lost my motivation.
Why don't you act towards me like I'm your real son, Mum?
Then will you study by yourself?
Sure.
OK, you can study as you please.
I'll go out to play.
Seriously!
Nobita, you're so stubborn.
I don't remember raising you to be like this!
My parents are so mean to me.
Of course, you're the one at fault, after all.
But she didn't had to abuse me like that...
Maybe...
Right, that must be it!
I must have been adopted by my parents.
I was probably adopted!
Don't say such things!
There's no way that you were...
But I'm sure of it!
Wherefore art though, my real mum?
OK, let's see what really happened using Time Machine!
Let's go to the day when you were born.
Right Why didn't I get this idea, earlier?
But what if I was adopted?
Don't be so suspicious. Hurry up and let's go!
To August 7, 10 years ago.
We're here!
This is our home, 10 years ago.
There are no maps and paintings yet.
Earlier in time, this used to be my dad's room.
Looks everyone's out.
Wonder why?
How was I born if my parents are nowhere to be found?
Right, you must have been adopted probably.
No way!
I'm just kidding! Surely your parents must be in hospital.
Where is my baby?
It's Daddy.
Hmm. So he's very young and handsome, 10 years ago.
Who're you two?
How could you forget the face of your own child?
Remember, you're not born yet.
Who are those two?
Never mind that, hurry and...
Where is my child?
He's nowhere to be found!
He's not here neither!
I came back from work
after I received the call.
Where is my baby?
You must go to hospital.
Ah... right
But who are you two, anyway?
You two are wandering in my home from a while...
Nevermind! I must rush to hospital!
Your father's anxious!
Wait, we will join you!
Congratulations, it's a boy.
Thanks for the food.
I mean, sorry... thanks...!
Uh...
I'm so excited!
I wonder how he looks...
I'm probably looking like the present me.
He must be a very lively baby
I become a father now.
He's got a big round face, just it's like his mother
The baby's there, dear.
Excuse me!
He's lively!
Let us have a look!
It's my baby form?
He has wrinkles all over his face, and he looks like a monkey.
How dare you say that!
Forgive us.
What's the deal with those children?
They're always following me.
I don't know what their parents have taught them
Name your son!
I've thought up of a decent name already.
Nobita
Nobi Nobita, don't you like the name?
I should ask them directly...
Don't do that! You'll be scolded again!
Of course it's a good name.
A long branch of a tree Extending smoothly, growing to the higher heights...
I hope he'll be a good boy.
Of course he's an excellent kid.
He'll be excellent in everything.
He'll be good at sports if he's like you.
He summarised all your weak points...
I'm very disappointed!
Will he be a scholar or a politician...
It'd have been nice if he became an artist.
Or even a Painter, Sculptor or a Musician.
Everything is good.
He has to be considerate...
Brave...
Be strong...
Fearless, Confident, Honour, Handsome...
Excuse us, but...
You're overestimating your son's capability.
He's not that special.
Really!
We must flee!
What did my son did to you two?
Who raised you two to be so stubborn!?
Now you know who your real parents are.
Aren't you happy?
My parents have put so much high hopes on me!
Nobita, you'll damage your health!
Please go to bed right this instant!
What's the matter with you?
Why are you studying so hard so suddenly?
Who knows how long this will last...